Guide to the Stan Healy Photographs and Papers 1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
Stan Healy Photographs and Papers
1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana, Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
Mss 430
Healy, "Stan" (Edward), 1918-1996
11.25 linear feet (approx. 4,050 images)
Edward "Stan" Healy was a Missoula, Montana, newspaper and freelance photographer and city council member. His collection includes news-oriented and other photographs taken in and around Missoula, mostly in the 1940s through the 1970s, as well as a small amount of personal photography, correspondence, and materials related to his time in the Army Air Force during World War II.
Biographical Note
Edward "Stan" Healy was born in Missoula, Montana, on July 19, 1918 to Edward and Emma Healy. He attended Whittier Grade School and graduated from Missoula County High School. In 1941, he graduated from the University of Montana with a bachelor's degree in journalism.
During World War II, Healy served in the U.S. Army from 1941 to 1945. In 1946, he began his career at the Missoulian as a reporter and photographer. He worked there until 1961, when he transitioned to freelance writing and photography. He worked primarily from Missoula but also traveled to other parts of the country to sell pictures to papers. He completed photo-based stories about Memphis, Tennessee, and the steel mills of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
Healy served on the Missoula City Council for seventeen years, representing Ward 2, the Northside Neighborhood. When Interstate Highway 90 was developed, the government demanded demolition of many Northside homes. Healy challenged the highway department to save his childhood home and others in the neighborhood. He was also interested in automobiles, cameras, electronics, and non-conforming modes of gender expression.
Healy suffered a heart attack in 1979, prompting his move to a nursing home. He died on March 27, 1996 in Missoula.
The Stan Healy Photographs and Papers consist primarily of photographs and materials from Healy’s career as a photo journalist and Missoula City Council member. The collection also contains a small amount of personal photography and correspondence, notes from Healy’s time at the University of Montana and his Army Air Force training during World War II, and materials related to his interest in cross-dressing.
Healy's photographs document Missoula, Montana, mostly from the 1940s through the 1970s. As a news photographer, he tended to document local news events, including automobile and railroad accidents, fires, and other tragedies. He also photographed changes in Missoula's built environment, including building construction and demolition and street work. Other favored subjects are parades, law enforcement, fire protection personnel, and the University of Montana. Several sweeping views and aerials of Missoula document the change and growth of the city.
Surrounding western Montana towns, including Bonner and Taft, are also documented in the collection. There are a considerable number of images of Northern Pacific Railway and Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad engines.
The collection contains a number of images taken by other photographers. Some predate Healy and may have come from the Missoulian photo morgue or from the studio of Frank Ingalls. Others are from fellow photographers John Forssen, Charles F. Buls (Healy’s maternal grandfather), A. Baker, H. English (of Wallace, Idaho), John Swartz, J.W. Meier, R.V. Nixon, R.H. McKay, and Norma Forsyth.
The collection is arranged in three series:
Series I: Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s, 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
Series II: Accession 2021-048 Photographs and Papers, circa 1930s-1990s, 4.0 linear feet (1,313 images)
Subseries 1: Negatives and slides, circa 1938-1960s
Subseries 2: Prints, circa 1930s-1990s
Subseries 3: Papers, 1935-1984
Series III: Charles F. Buls Family Photographs, circa 1890s, 0.75 linear feet (37 images)
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and the University of Montana--Missoula.
Photos of scenes involving murder and crime victims, which Healy covered on several occasions, have been restricted by the Archives until 2056 due to the nature of the content.
The photographs in Series I were held by Stan Healy and his trust before they were purchased by the Friends of the Library in 1990. Most of the items in Series II were held by Kathleen Kimble, a family friend, until they were donated to the University of Montana in 2021, with the exception of one photograph, which was purchased by collector Tim Gordon who later resold it to the University of Montana. Custodial information about Series III photographs is unknown.
Stan Healy donated one photo to the University of Montana in June 1983. The Friends of the Library, a nonprofit organization, purchased the bulk of the photos in Series I in June 1990 from Stan Healy’s trust. In October of 2001, the University of Montana purchased an additional Healy photo from Tim Gordon. On April 26, 2021, Kathleen Kimble signed a deed of gift transferring additional Stan Healy photographs and papers to the University of Montana. Acquisition information about Series III photographs is unknown.
Additional Healy photographs and some of Healy's personal papers are held by Tim Gordon of Missoula.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Baker, A.; Buls, Charles F.; English, H.; Forssen, John A., 1916-1995; Ingalls, F. M. (Frank M.), 1861-1934
Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railroad Company; Northern Pacific Railway Company; University of Montana--Missoula--Alumni and alumnae; University of Montana--Missoula--Photographs
Bonner (Mont.)--Photographs; Missoula (Mont.)--Buildings, structures, etc. -- Photographs; Missoula (Mont.)--Photographs; Taft (Mont.)--Photographs
Fire fighters--Monatna -- Missoula--Photographs; Fires--Montana -- Missoula--Photographs; Law enforcement--Montana --Missoula--Photographs; Locomotives--Montana -- Photographs; Parades--Montana -- Missoula--Photographs; Photojournalism--Montana --Missoula.; Railroad accidents -- Montana--Missoula--Photographs; Traffic accidents -- Montana--Missoula--Photographs
Photographs--Montana -- Missoula
Idaho; Montana; Photographs; Architecture; City and Town Life; Transportation
News photographers -- Montana--Missoula; Photographers--Idaho --Wallace; Photographers--Montana --Missoula
- Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
  Series I features photographs taken by Stan Healy during the course of his career as a journalist and freelance photographer for the Missoulian and other newspapers as well as his tenure as a Missoula City Council alderman. Most of photos in this series were shot in and around Missoula, Montana, and document local news events.
  Items within this series are organized by photo number.
  - Ranch buildings at Hell Gate, Montana, 3 miles west of Missoula on Mullan Road, September 1947 (Box 1, Photo number 87-0281)
  - Main Street of Hell Gate looking east; Worden Store, right center, September 1947 (Box 1, Photo number 87-0282)
  - Oxford Bar at night, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 88-0056)
  - Missoula Police Department in front of City Hall, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0174)
  - Old Missoula City Hall, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0175)
  - Old Missoula City Hall, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0176)
  - Old Missoula City Hall, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0177)
  - Missoula County Sheriff's Department (?), on steps of courthouse, circa 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0178)
  - Missoula County Sheriff's Department (?), on steps of courthouse, circa 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0179)
  - Missoula County Sheriff's Department (?), on steps of courthouse, circa 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0180)
  - Missoula city police, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0181)
  - Missoula city police, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0182)
  - Missoula city police, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0183)
  - Missoula Brewing Company building being dismantled, November 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0184)
  - Missoula Brewing Company building being dismantled, November 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0185)
  - Missoula Brewing Company building being dismantled, November 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0186)
  - Missoula Brewing Company building being dismantled, November 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0187)
  - Missoula Brewing Company building being dismantled, November 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0188)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, vat for brewing, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0189)
  - Fire Department personnel surveying fire damage at the Highlander Brewery, Missoula, Montana, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0190A)
  - Fire Department personnel surveying fire damage at the Highlander Brewery, Missoula, Montana, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0190B)
  - Missoula Brewing Company fire, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0191)
  - Missoula Brewing Company fire, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0192)
  - Missoula Brewing Company fire, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0193)
  - Missoula Brewing Company fire, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0194)
  - Missoula Brewing Company fire, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0195)
  - Missoula Brewing Company fire, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0196)
  - Missoula Brewing Company fire, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0197)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0198)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0199)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1964 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0200)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0201)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1965 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0202)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1965 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0203)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1965 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0204)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1965 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0205)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1965 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0206)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1965 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0207)
  - Missoula Brewing Company, circa 1965 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0208)
  - Florence Hotel, soda fountain, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0209)
  - Florence Hotel, soda fountain, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0210)
  - Florence Hotel, soda fountain, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0211)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0212)
  - Greenough Mansion, move, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0213)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0214)
  - Greenough Mansion, on Farviews after move, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0215)
  - Greenough Mansion, on Farviews after move, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0216)
  - Greenough Mansion, former site along freeway, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0217)
  - Greenough Mansion, former site along freeway, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0218)
  - Greenough Mansion, before move, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0219)
  - Greenough Mansion, on original site, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0220)
  - KYSS radio, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0221)
  - KYSS radio, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0222)
  - KYSS radio, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0223)
  - Ormesher Market (formerly Deschamps Imports) on Main and Ryman Streets, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0224)
  - Chamber of Commerce and Liberty Bowling buildings on East Main, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0225)
  - Turmell Tire Company, West Main Steet, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0226)
  - Florence Hotel, construction of parking garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0227)
  - Florence Hotel, bridge tournament in lobby, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0228)
  - Florence Hotel, bridge tournament in lobby, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0229)
  - Florence Hotel, bridge tournament in lobby, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0230)
  - Florence Hotel, bridge tournament in lobby, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0231)
  - Florence Hotel, bridge tournament in lobby, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0232)
  - American Legion building, fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0233)
  - American Legion building, fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0234)
  - American Legion building, fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0235)
  - American Legion building, fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0236)
  - American Legion building, fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0237)
  - American Legion building, fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0238)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0239)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0240)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0241)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0242)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0243)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0244)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0245)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0246)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0247)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0248)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0249)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0250)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0251)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0252)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0253)
  - Hillside Club, old University of Montana Dornblaser Field, last day, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0254)
  - Logging truck accident, load of logs dumped on East Broadway Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0255)
  - Logging truck accident, load of logs dumped on East Broadway Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0256)
  - Florence Hotel, building parking garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0257)
  - Florence Hotel, interior office, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0258)
  - Florence Hotel, completed parking garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0259)
  - Florence Hotel, building parking garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0260)
  - Florence Hotel, building parking garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0261)
  - Florence Hotel, parking garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0262)
  - University of Montana campus, Simkins "Little Theater", undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0263)
  - West Broadway Avenue, night scene, Missoula Hotel, circa 1957 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0264)
  - Higgins Bank building, corner of Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0265)
  - West Main Street, Zip Auto in background, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0266)
  - Southwest corner, Higgins Avenue and Main Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0267)
  - Shoe store display window, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0268)
  - West Main Street, Flame Lounge, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0269)
  - D'Orazi Grocery, corner Woody and Alder Streets, being demolished, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0270)
  - D'Orazi Grocery, corner Woody and Alder Streets, being demolished, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0271)
  - D'Orazi Grocery, corner Woody and Alder Streets, being demolished, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0272)
  - D'Orazi Grocery, corner Woody and Alder Streets, being demolished, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0273)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0274)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0275)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0276)
  - Keith Hotel, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0277)
  - Keith Hotel, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0278)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0279)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0280)
  - Hart Shoe Repair, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0281)
  - Hart Shoe Repair, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0282)
  - Hart Shoe Repair, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0283)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0284)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0285)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0286)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0287)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0288)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0289)
  - In-B-Tween Bar, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0290)
  - In-B-Tween Bar, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0291)
  - In-B-Tween Bar, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0292)
  - In-B-Tween Bar, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0293)
  - In-B-Tween Bar, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0294)
  - In-B-Tween Bar, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0295)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0296)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0297)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0298)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0299)
  - Keith Hotel, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0300)
  - Keith Hotel, Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0301)
  - Alley off Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0302)
  - Alley off Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0303)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0304)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0305)
  - Woody Street, D'Orazi Grocery, Missoula, Montana, circa 1970 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0306)
  - Woody Street, D'Orazi Grocery, Missoula, Montana, circa 1970 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0307)
  - Woody Street, D'Orazi Grocery, Missoula, Montana, circa 1970 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0308)
  - Woody Street, D'Orazi Grocery, Missoula, Montana, circa 1970 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0309)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0310)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0311)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0312)
  - Woody Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1968 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0313)
  - Looking from Bitterroot Railroad bridge on Clark Fork toward Mount Sentinel, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 1, Photo number 90-0314)
  - Looking west from Higgins Avenue bridge, Missoula, Montana, September 7, 1955 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0315)
  - Main Street, looking east from Ryman Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0316)
  - Main Street, looking east from Ryman Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0317)
  - Higgins Avenue, Lucy Furniture (?), Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0318)
  - Northern Pacific Railway Depot, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0319)
  - Parade on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0320)
  - Stockman Bar on West Front Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0321)
  - Daily Meat Market, Front Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0322)
  - Daily Meat Market, Front Street, Missoula, Montana, circa 1950 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0323)
  - Oldsmobile car dealer, Missoula, Montana, August 8, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0324)
  - Oldsmobile car dealer, Missoula, Montana, August 8, 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0325)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company interior, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0326)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company interior, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0327)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company car dealership, front desk, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0328)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0329)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics working on cars, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0330)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics working on cars, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0331)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics working on cars, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0332)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics working on cars, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0333)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0334)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0335)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0336)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0337)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0338)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0339)
  - H.O. Bell Ford Company, mechanics, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 1, Photo number 90-0340)